earlier it
раньше
was Crimea and all of Ukraine that belonged to
именно Крым и вся Украина принадлежала
Russia because well how then they gave the
России потому что ну как потом дали
territory earlier this is when earlier this is sometime well
территорию раньше это когда раньше это
I'm honest And even earlier and even
когда-то ну я честно А ещё раньше а ещё
earlier who did it
Раньше кому
belong to remember this Great Battle of the
принадлежало помните это Великую битву
Neanderthals with
неандертальцев с
the Cro-Magnon Good afternoon I'm from the city of
кроманьонца Добрый день Я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from I'm from the Far
Хмельницкий Вы откуда я с Дальнего
East Khabarovsk Krai cool yeah
Востока Хабаровский край прикольно да О
What do you talk about eh
чём общаетесь
just talking to people like
э просто общаюсь с людьми типа о
what am I just talking about there is no exact
чём просто общаюсь нет никакой точной
goal just communication got it let's just
цели просто общение понял давайте Просто
chat Why did Russia attack
пообщаемся Почему Россия напала на на
Ukraine What do you think Well you know
Украину Как вы думаете Ну знаете вот
few people ask such questions But I don't have a
немногие такие вопросы задают Но у меня
precise answer because Well not me
нет точного ответа потому что Ну не я же
not on your feeling here for 2 years already a
не на ваше ощущение вот 2 года уже
full-scale 10 years there has been a
полномасштабное 10 лет идёт вторжение
2 years full-scale invasion of Russia into Ukraine
России в Украину 2 года полномасштабное
how do you feel
Вторжение как вы ощущаете
Why I don't know I
Почему я не знаю мне
somehow don't care probably and from your
как-то всё равно наверное а из ваших
friends there are already someone someone
знакомых друзей уже есть кто-то кого-то
was taken to Ukraine to
забрали на Украину
fight no It's interesting somehow and from your
воевать нет Интересно как-то а из вашего
city you know there have already been dead in Ukraine Yes a
города Вы знаете погибших в Украине уже
lot
Да много
M not so many but that's it  equal Just you don't
М не так много но всё равно Просто вы не
know yes all Deta Yes I understand But the
знаете да всех Дета Да понял А вот
question is why are they in Ukraine
вопрос ради чего они в Украине
Well, as most citizens think, for the sake of the
Ну как думают большая часть граждан ради
Motherland, but it doesn't seem to me, just like that, let's go, it's
Родины но мне так не кажется просто так
cool, listen, the death of people is
прикольно слушайте смерть людей это
very cool It's
очень прикольно Просто прикольно люди
just cool, people come to another country, just
приезжают в другую страну просто коро
for
ради
what, the test of the
чего тест
Russian Federation, I also ask how do
Российской Федерации тоже спрашиваю как
you see it Well, the government is also just
вы это видите Ну правительство ж просто
it represents the interests of citizens
тоже оно представляет интересы граждан
You Yeah Well, I wonder how people, here,
Вас Угу Ну мне интересно как люди вот
ordinary ordinary people look at all this,
Обычный простой народ смотрят на это всё
no, look at some people, well,
не ну смотрите некоторых людей вот ну
almost some people Well, war is a
почти некоторых людей Ну война - это как
way of earning money if they manage to
способ заработка если у них получится
earn money,
заработать
of course, that
конечно у то
is, for people like me, war is
есть для таких как я война - это
negative Well, I'm against war
отрицательно Ну я против войны потому
because, that is, it turns out that the Russian
что то есть получается Российская
Russian army is just people
российская армия - это просто люди
who went to earn money to kill,
которые поехали заработать бабла на уби
please Well, I'm not interrupting you Well, I'll
пожалуйста Ну я же вас не перебиваю Ну я
clarify right away Did I understand correctly that they
сразу Уточняю Я правильно понял что они
earn money That's why they go to
зарабатывают деньги Поэтому и едут в
Ukraine to kill Yes, not all Not all Not all,
Украину убивать Да не все Не все Не все
some against their will because at
некоторые против воли потому что в
the moment, where I live, when there
данный момент где я живу у нас когда
was a full mobilization, Well, not a full
была полная мобилизация Ну не полная
mobilization, they just forced us to go
просто мобилизация нас заставляли ехать
to war
на войну
That is, they just people  they don't want to but they were
То есть просто людей они не хотят а их
taken because they were needed in the army Yes, there
брали потому что нужно в армии Да
was someone
кого-то было
Dania, this is interesting in order to
Даня это интересно для того чтобы
attack a foreign country, they were
напасть на чужую страну их насильно
taken away by force, interesting yes And by the way, what do you
забирали интересно да А кстати вот вы
personally think whose
лично как считаете чей
Crimea is? I don't know, most likely Russia,
Крым Я не знаю скорее всего России
because Well, earlier, it was
потому что Ну раньше
Crimea and all of Ukraine that belonged to
именно Крым и вся Украина принадлежала
Russia, because well, how then they gave the
России потому что ну как потом дали
territory to Russia, this is the
территорию раше это
code for a,
кода кото
and even earlier, and even earlier, to whom did it
а ещ раньше а ещ Раньше кому
belong? It belonged to the Russian
принадлежало это принадлежало Российской
Empire. And before the Russian Empire,
империи А до Российской
why not someone, I understood, yes, like, well, to whom did
че не кто-то я понял да вот типа ну Кому
it
оно
belong? I have no idea, I'm not a historian, [ __ ],
принадлежало Без понятия я не историк
look, it belonged to, I remember, there was still,
сри смотри принадлежало помню ещ были
remember, the Great Battle with the Canyon The Hundred Years'
помните Великую битву с каньон Столетняя
War was called Yes, then the Canyon
война называлась Да вот тогда каньон
was defeated Yes, and in principle, they occupied this
победили Да вот и в принципе заняли эту
territory So what was that, yes, that's how the
территорию Так что было такое да то та
Cro-Magnons
кроманьонцы
reign now the question is yes, it was like that
теперь царствуют вопрос такой да было
before one kingdom came the second, the
так до одно царство приходило второе
third, they fell apart, disappeared, here is the
третье распадались пропадали вот есть
year 1991, an
девяносто первый год
independent state of
да появилась независимое государство
Ukraine and an independent state of the
Украина и независимое государство
Russian Federation appeared, yes, two
Российская Федерация так да два
independent states within their borders,
независимых государства в своих границах
these states
эти государства международными
recognized each other's borders by international treaties
договорами признали границы друг
friend yes yes then what difference does it make what is there
друга да да то какая разница что там
when where What was And so on Yes
когда где Что было И так дальше Да
Belgorod He was also in Ukraine at one
Белгород Он тоже был в Украине в своё
time That's what if Crimea is part of Ukraine and
время Вот то если Крым часть Украины и
Russia recognized it yes How can we
Россия это признала да Как мы можем
now say that Crimea is
сейчас говорить что Крым - это
Russia well I'm burning with it But it seems to me that it
Россия ну горю это Но мне кажется он
belongs to Russia and in general
принадлежит России да и вообще Вот вы
Now you are discussing the war there and all that but have
сейчас обсуждаете войну там всё такое но
you undertaken something so that well I don't know undertaken undertaken
вы что-то предприняли чтобы ну я не знаю
yes look we are
предприняли предприняли да смотрите мы
collecting huge collections for
собираем огромные сборы на дроны
kamikaze drones for drones Bombers for RBR systems
камикадз на дроны Бомберы на системы рбр
so that more of these occupiers
для того чтобы побольше этих оккупантов
who are arriving including your city
которые прилетом числе и вашего города
Yes to Ukraine so that they can quickly
Да в Украину чтобы они побыстрее
go home either alive or in
отправились домой либо живыми либо по
parts
частям
no So Wait are you against the war or for
нет Так Подождите вы против войны или за
I am against the war I want Well so I
Я против войны Я хочу чтобы Ну так я
want it to end look the
хочу чтобы она закончилась смотрите
war started because of What because of The fact that
война началась из-за Чего из-за Того что
the occupiers came to our Land yes that
оккупанты пришли на нашу Землю да то
is in order for the war to end we
есть для того чтобы закончилась война
need to kill them quickly and more so that some die
надо побыстрее и побольше их убить чтобы
some run away yes that is
часть умерла часть убежала да то есть
if we help our army Yes with all sorts of
если мы помогаем нашей армии Да всякими
different interesting things  which
разными штучками интересными которые
help faster denazification
помогают быстрее денацификация
then faster peace will come this is logical
то быстрее наступит мир это же логично
this is illogical how illogical it
это нелогично как нелогично Это очень
sounds very stupid because A how A how should one
глупо звучит потому что А как А как надо
be For peace For example Russia attacked
быть За мир Вот например Россия напала
Ukraine what should people in Ukraine do
на Украину что делать людям в Украине
who are For peace don't wait So you don't
которые За мир не подождите Так вы не
generalize without
обобщается не
generalizing well yeah well the state Yes look the
обобщая вот да ну государство Да смотри
state brought these soldiers Yes
государство привело вот этих солдат Да
Russian if in Ukraine those who are For peace
российское если в Украине те кто За мир
how should they act well
как они должны действовать вот обни
I don't know there are some petitions to
интересно я не знаю там петиции какие-то
sign
подписывать
Well there are many decisions for whom petitions to
Ну много решений есть кому петиции
sign the state to stop
подписывать государству чтобы прекратили
this war Russian year that is under
эту войну российскому года то есть подо
I just didn't understand We should
Я просто не понял Мы должны Путину
write to Putin don't wait now I'll tell you it's
писать не подождите сейчас я вам скажу
not easier Just take and recognize and
вот не проще Просто взять и признать и
give this Crimea or I don't
отдать этот Крым или я не
know so much is needed to lose
знаю так сильно нужен чтобы терять
Millions of people
Миллионы людей
Kyiv also
Киев тоже отдать
needs to be given Who are you I understand you're
нужно Кто ты Я понял ты третий раз
repeating for the third time what are you for
повторяешь что ты
Why are you repeating this I see
зачем Да зачем ты это повторяешь Я вижу
like Yes I don't need to emphasize this
типа Да мне не надо на это акцентировать
you that is look it turns out I
ты то есть смотри получается я правильно
understand correctly that for example when Hitler attacked the
понимаю что например когда Гитлер напал
Soviet Union yes then Stalin had to
на Советский Союз да то Сталину нужно
agree with the sweat
было согласиться с поте
territory wanted  enslave the whole world And what does
територи хотел поработить весь мир А что
Russia want to enslave you no so
Россия хочет вас поработить нет так
look he captured Look here would have
смотрите он захватил Смотри вот
stopped for example on the Volga for
остановилось бы например по Волге
example yes
например да
Germany unpacked Yes for the world that
Германии распаковал Да за мирове
I am from the city of Khmelnitsky Where are you
та Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
from the city of Pyatigorsk about the North Caucasus
откуда город Пятигорск о Северный Кавказ
Yes Cool And who by
Да Прикольно А кто по
nationality is a mestizo Well there is no such
национальности метис Ну нет такой
nationality mestizo Well part Russian
национальности метис Ну часть русский
part Abazin I understood it is Circassian yes it
часть абазин понял это черкес да
turns out yes it is some well next to
получается да это какой-то ну рядом с
Circassians live Abazin you are not Circassians Well this is It is an
черкесами живут абазин сы не черкесы Ну
Adyghe people hellish people
это Это ж адыгский народы адский народ
Yes that's right hellish people it's all like an
Да правильно адский народ это всё типа
Adyghe group there now they have
адыгская группа там сейчас они
divided there into Circassians Adyghe there what
разделились там на черкесы Адыги там шо
Kabardins yes in short yes yes yes yes yes I understand and how do you
кабардинцы да короча да дадада да понял
communicate here
а чём общаетесь тут
Yes so just talking with people how is the
Да так просто с людьми разговариваю как
situation in Ukraine in general how are people What do they
вообще обстановка на Украине как люди О
think about In general what do they say
чём думают Вообще что говорят Нормально
The situation is normal awesome they think in short
обстановка офигенно думают чтобы короче
more pig-dogs
побольше свинособак
In short that's what they talk about Today for
Короче так об этом и говорят Вот сегодня
example today everyone watched the video of
например сегодня все смотрели видео как
this pig-dog ship  sunk like
этот корабль свино собачий потопили типа
Feodosia on the Black Sea Generally cool with a
на Чёрном море Феодосии Вообще кайф с
helicopter together yes yes it is with
вертолётом вместе да
water drones helicopter Here you are a
жа водными дронами вертол
blogger Yes probably yes now I am
Вот вы блогер Да наверное да сейчас
streaming I have
Стрим
such an interesting question Well
иду у меня вот вопрос такой интересный А
why is a
ну почему
serviceman of any country Well let's
военнослужащего любого страны Ну пускай
even assume If as you reason the
даже допустим Если как вы рассуждаете
aggressor countries of Russia consider, for example, an
страны агрессора России считают например
insult if he is simply doing
в оскорбление если он просто выполняет
his duty which is prescribed to him
свой дол который ему прописан
Yes look We are not servicemen of any
Да смотрите Мы ж не военнослужащих любой
country this is a specific country I call Well exactly let's
страны это конкретной страны называю Ну
say Russia Why
именно вот допустим России Почему
look if they send to kill other
смотрите если отправляют убивать других
people Yes on order not on order she does
людей Да по приказу не по приказу она же
not stop from everyday life from this If she
не перестаёт от этого быт если она
came to kill people how does it mean I will
пришла убивать людей как значит я
interrupt And what about the units,
перебью А как насчёт подразделений
say, support which Well do not take
скажем обеспечения которые Ну не
part in hostilities
принимают участие в боевых действия
accept accept look the one who
принимают принимают смотри тот кто
delivers cartridges he also participates in the
подвозит патроны он тоже участвует в
killing of people the one who delivers missiles
убийстве людей тот кто подвозит ракеты
caliber Yes also participates in the killing of
калибр Да тоже участвует в убийстве
people Well he is Well here on How to
людей Ну он же является Ну вот на Как
say
сказать
He is doing his just to Let's do it this way
Он выполняет свой просто до Давай так
if he had not delivered this ammunition
если бы он не подвёз эти боеприпасы
people would not have been killed
людей бы не убили
right Well he was ordered to do it
правильно Ну ему приказали это сделать
right  ordered But if he is
правильно приказали А вот если ему
ordered to kill a
прикажут убить
person, criminal orders The thing is that there is
человека преступные приказы Дело в том
such a thing under your
что есть такое по вашему
legislation, too, no one is obliged to
законодательству тоже никто не обязан
carry out A criminal order Yes, it is a
исполнять Преступный приказ Да это
criminal order because your
Преступный приказ потому что ваш
president started an aggressive war against a
президент начал агрессивную войну против
foreign state if you were attacked
чужого государства если бы на вас напали
And you were given the order to defend yourself then it was
И вам дали приказ защититься тогда было
clear that this was a sacred thing for them Yes And
понятно это святое дело было у них Да А
so they were given the order some dwarf from the
так Им дали приказ какой-то карлик из
Kremlin gave the order to go and kill people in
Кремля дал приказ идти и убивать людей в
another country for 2 years already to kill And would you
другой стране 2 года уже убивать А вы бы
call your fellow countrymen
называли своих земляков
if they attacked us, for example, it is
если бы они напали на нас например
difficult for me to understand why we would climb to
мне трудно понять зачем мы бы полезли на
attack you Well, it does not matter Why did
вас нападать Ну не имеет значени Почему
your president simply want, for example, to squeeze
просто ваш президент захотел например
out the Belgorod region or
отжать Белгородскую область или
Kukuy, where did he fight in World War II
кукуй де воевал во Второй мировой войне
Yes, against Hitler, so that's how My grandfather, yes,
Да против Гитлера так вот Мой дед да
what words did not call the
Какими только словами не называл
fascists, the Germans, and how in the Soviet Union
фашистов немцев и как в Советском Союзе
we, what is good They talked about the Germans, about the
мы что хорошо О немцах говорили о
fascists, no, they
фашистах нет
invented for these Nazis,
изобретали для этих нацистов
just in every possible way and Hali is normal, so
просто по-всякому и Хали нормально так и
here you are the aggressor That's all
тут вы агрессор Всё
you, if we are on you  attacked Yes we were for
вы если мы на вас напали Да мы были для
you But no
вас А
that's not the question M I understood that let's say I mean you would
так нет не в том вопрос М я понял что
say Russia
говорите Россия на ва
attacked Russia would you count your fellow countrymen
напала на Россию вы бы своих земляков
or would you specifically look would
считали или вы конкретно вот смотрите вы
you definitely count us if we
вы бы точно нас считали если бы мы на
attacked you No it's us Wait it's us you
вас напали Нет это мы Подождите это мы
specifically You as a person would you
вы конкретно Вот вы как личность вы бы
count your fellow countrymen You are against the
считали своих земляков Вот вы же против
war if for example if we had the
войны полу если если у нас например там
president say let's go
сказал бы президент давайте мы на пойдём
to Moldova And start killing people in
на Молдову И начали бы убивать людей в
Chisinau There and so on Yes
Кишинёве Там и так дальше Да просто бы
we would just want to because
нам так захотелось потому что это
historically during Bohdan
исторически во время Богдана
Khmelnitsky's time it was shorter there or there Lyp
Хмельницкого было короче там или там лып
Orly there in Bendery he also wrote
орлы там тоже в Бендерах писал
his Constitution
Конституцию свою Да
Yes we would be aggressors and bad ones
вот мы мы бы были агрессорами да плохими
No I understood that specifically you as a
Нет я понял чтобы конкретно вы как
person let's say as a
человек вот допустим как
person you now Yes you want if
личность ты сейчас Да хочешь если бы
now there is a fact Russia attacked
сейчас есть факт Россия напала на
Ukraine Yes we are not hypothetically
Украину Да вот мы не гипотетически
looking we are really yes Russia attacked
смотрим мы реально да Россия напала
Russia everything everything is simple That is all No not
Россия всё всё просто То есть
all there are those who are there are those
все Нет не все есть те которые есть те
who are against In Russia too for
которые выступают против В России тоже
example  They set fire to railroads Yes,
например поджигают железные дороги Да
they set fire to military registration and enlistment offices Yes, they blew up a bridge
поджигают военкоматы Да мост взорвали
there, that's
вот там вот это
not good, but if someone is neutral,
не хорошо а если кто на нейтралитете
who doesn't want war either
находится который не хочет ни войны ни
against Russia or against Ukraine, or if they are
против России ни против Украины Нели на
neutral, that's
нейтралитете этоже
morality, his silence is legal, there is
мораль пон его молчание в праве есть
such a concept as action and
такое понятие действие и
inaction, and so on Yes, you are
бездеятельный так дальше Да вы несёте
also
тоже
responsible in the law, there is nothing
ответственность в законе же ничего
like that described, there is, that's what it's
такого об этом не описано есть есть так
called Yes, what exactly, what if I
и называется Да что именно что если я
saw a person being killed, I got scared and
увидел как убивают человека испугался и
left that place
ушёл с этого места
Yes, can you imagine Yes, you are
Да вы представляете Да вы
guilty What am I guilty of if my
виноваты В чём я виноват если мои
physical capabilities don't allow it
физические возможности не позволяют
Nothing, yes If they don't allow it You should have
Ничего если да Если не позволяют Вы
reported it to the police Yes, that's how it's
должны были сообщить в полицию Да что
happening here, like an
вот тут так и так происходит типа
offense, they kill a
правонарушение убивают
person, but that's not a story about
человека а так это не не повем про
crimes, I don't know how it sounds to you, not a
злочин не знаю как это по-вашему звучит
report of a crime,
не сообщение преступлени ещ раз
repeat it again, I'll tell you a
повторите я скажу вам
report of a
сообщение о
crime Well, in the form of something like that Yes, well,
преступлении Ну в виде так такого
I'm
Да ну я
here, yes Yes, let's do it At a party Yes, uh, there were
здесь да Дава давайте так На вечеринке
five people in the room,
ээ было да пять человек было в комнате
two girls Yes, and three were just watching,
двое девушку Да а трое просто смотрели
they were
они
Accomplices if they were standing right next to each other  then yes
Соучастники если стояли рядом прям то да
If they physically can't
Если они не физически не могут ничего
do anything then no what do they have to do with
сделать то нет какого отношения Они к
it I physically can't do
этому имеют я вот физически не могу
anything what can I Well I'll come up and
ничего сделать что я могу Ну я подойду
say you can't do this You're
скажу этого нельзя делать Вы там
criminals there They'll give it to me and that's it Well in
преступники Мне дадут и всё я ну по
fact nothing And that I'm a hero in this no
факту ничего И что я герой в этом нет не
you're an
вы
accomplice just well here it's not violence you
соучастник просто ну тут же не насилие
know how there is a
получается знаете как вот есть
serviceman Yes the Russian Federation uh he has an
военнослужащий Да РФ э у него есть там
order there for example yes There is no such order to
ну приказ например да Нету такого прика
kill civilians there or kill
убивать там граждански или убивать там
something there Kra or looters Ma also suppresses
чтото кра или мародёры ма тоже пресекает
look look Hello calm down you started to
смотри смотри Алло успокойся ты начал
pile on look come on what order are the
наваливать смотри давай так какой приказ
prisoners executing who are thrown to kill
исполняет зки которых бросают убивать
people in
людей в
Ukraine I don't know the army specifically didn't
Украине Я не знаю армия конкретно не
call up prisoners And who
призывала зеков А кто их
called them up is a PMC it has nothing to do with the army
призывал это чвк это Никакой к арми
Wait is that the
отношения не имеет Подожди это что
state has nothing to
государство не имеет никакого
do with it Well it's some kind of private
отношения Ну это какая-то частная
military company wait some kind of private
военная компания подожди какая-то частна
pppp I heard from everyone Russia says that
пппп слышал от всех Россия говорит что
Russia captured
Россия захватила
Bakhmut it doesn't say that some
бахмут она не говорит что какая-то
private company captured Bakh they say Russia
частная компания захватила Бах говорят
Yes Putin  he himself said yes that the
Россия Да Путин сам говорил да что чвк
Wagner PMC financed from the
Вагнер финансировал из
budget Well yes, there are probably no questions about
бюджета Ну да вопросов наверное нет в
this I'm not strong in these questions further In
этом не силён в этих вопросов дальше
short, look What do you want to cry about
Короче смотрите Что вы хотите поплакать
you want to say that you are not guilty
вы хотите сказать что вы не виноваты ни
of anything Yes no I'm not saying innocence I
в чём Да нет я не говорю невиновности я
specifically latched onto the
конкретно зацепился за
insult of a person even because he is
оскорбление человека даже от того что он
g Pony Pony Understood Understood Question understood Look a
г Поня Поня Понял Вопрос понял Смотри
conscript is not a conscript at all yes then the
срочник не срочник вообще да
war will end then all the Russians
вот закончится война тогда все русские
who do not consider themselves Yes we just
которые не считают себя Да у нас просто
have a special body yes to which it will be
есть специальный орган да в который
possible to submit an application that I
можно будет подавать заявление что
ask to exclude me from the register
прошу исключить меня из реестра потому
because I and justify what you are doing in order to
что я и обосновывать что вы дела для
stop this war we have a
того чтобы остановить эту войну у нас
special commission Yes from veterans of
специальная комиссия Да из ветеранов
military operations Yes it will sit and
боевых действий Да будет заседать и
will consider these for example here
будет рассматривать эти например вот
will be
будет
Yeah a person writes I fought in the RDC everything is
Ага человек пишет Я воевал в РДК всё
clear no he fought against the
однозначно нет он воевал против
Russian Federation Yes a Nazi
Российской Федерации Да нацистской
person writes I blew up in the city of Samara
человек пишет Я в городе Самара взорвал
for example
например
there a post all that Pete I sat and waited in short
там пост всё тот Пит я сидел ждал короче
re Reject and that's it the Supreme Court is very
ре Отклонить и всё то есть ВС очень
simple Well you have a very narrow understanding in
просто Ну у вас очень узкое понимание в
this regard you reason like that you yourself
этом плане вы так рассуждаете вы сами
were somewhere here  Well, in combat
были где-то вот ну в боевых действиях
No, I wasn't And why do you reason like that
Нет не был А почему вы так рассуждаете
relatively here even many
относительно вот даже многие
yut I'm changing my mind for a second of course Many of your
ют я на секунду пере конечно Многие ваши
servicemen even in
военнослужащие даже вот в
RTM many Russians fight there to the
ртм многие русские сражаются там до
last they are from a military point of view
последнего они с военной точки зрения
some kind of at all look at all everything doesn't matter
какие-то вообще смотри вообще вс всё всё
what they say but they exist who
равно что говорят но они есть которые
attacked our country all they can be
напали на нашу страну всё они могут быть
super warriors in short super robots
супер воинами короче супер роботами
in general you know why
вообще знаете за
someone can't be a warrior of something and what by order
воином кого-то чего-то и что по приказу
And if they order him you
А если ему прикажут
want to say that you for all the time I'm
хочете сказать что вы за всё время я
asking I'm asking if this
спра Я спрашиваю Я спрашиваю если этому
soldier tells the prisoner
солдату скажет пленного
he No of course in the mouth because in his
он Нет конечно в уста потому что у него
charter charter there is no one should
уставе уставе есть никто не должен
carry out criminal orders And this is a criminal
исполнять преступные приказы А это
order
Преступный приказ
what to enter the territory of Ukraine Here is the
какой войти на территорию Украины Вот и
Armed Forces and why is it criminal
ВС а почему он является преступным
this is aggression against another
это агрессия против другого
state and what do you have in your
государства и что у ва у вас в
criminal code now I'll
криминально в Уголовном кодексе сейчас
tell you what this article is called for
скажу как эта статья называется за
unleashing an aggressive war Yes, the Criminal Code of the
развязывание агрессивной войны Да
Russian Federation so here is Article 335 of the Criminal Code of the Russian Federation
УКРФ так вот 335 статья УКРФ
planning preparation for unleashing or
планирование подготовка развязывания или
waging an aggressive war That is,
ведение агрессивной войны Вот то есть
pun yoke,
пун иго
here are the
вот
crimes according to your
преступлени по вашему
legislation in your
законодательству в вашем
legislation there is such an article no
законодательстве есть такая статья вот
one
никто не
should follow the orders of a criminal
должен исполнять приказы преступника
who planned,
который спланировал
prepared, unleashed and is waging an aggressive
подготовил развязал и ведёт агрессивную
war it's
войну это ж
simple look planning,
просто вот смотрите планирование
preparation or unleashing of an aggressive war
подготовка или развязывание агрессивной
imprisonment for a term of 7 to 15 years
лишением свободы На срок от 7 до 15 лет
waging an aggressive war That is, those who
ведение агрессивной войны То есть те кто
seem to follow the order fall
вроде как исполняют приказ попадают
waging an aggressive war Punishable by
ведение агрессивной войны Наказывается
imprisonment for a term of 10 to 20 years
лишением свободы На срок от 10 до 20 лет
that is, they committed aggression against
то есть они сделали агрессию против
another state That is, according to all
другого государства То есть это по всем
international norms it is an aggressive
международным нормам агрессивная
war and according to your legislation it is
война и по вашему законодательству это
punishable by the Armed Forces there is
карается ВС есть
for planning, preparation and
за планирование подготовку и
unleashing of an aggressive war and all who
развязывание агрессивной войны а все кто
carry out his criminal orders
исполняет его преступные приказы
waging an aggressive war everything is
заведение агрессивной войны всё
simple Yes, everything is very simple with you to be
просто Да у вас очень всё просто если
honest Well, it's not me who
честно Ну это ж ваше законодательство не
came up with your legislation Well, ours Well, an order is an
придумал Ну наше Да ну приказ он есть
order You
приказ Вы
know I know I have this order is an order an
знаете я е раз сю приказ есть
order is an order
прика приказ есть приказ
True Well, you
Правда Ну вы тоже
compare too That is, if I'm standing in a
сравнивайте То есть если я стою в
room in which a girl of course I will be an
комнате в который девушку конечно я буду
accomplice I will not take action A  if I
соучастником не приму действия А если я
am on the same floor in this regard then I am not
нахожусь на одном этаже в этом плане то
again look if the
не являюсь не ещё раз смотрите если
commander orders your
командир прикажет вашему
this girl because she should give up
это девушку потому что чтобы она выдала
where the Partisans are
где Партизаны
sitting he is her for the purposes of the state
сидят он её в целях государства
No we will report that he will go to
Нет мы доложим о том что он пойдёт по
court for such actions these are cruel
трибунал за такие действия это жестокие
actions in relation to such a situation
действия по отношению вот такой ситуации
Who of the Russians went to court in 2 years
Кто из за 2 года из россиян пошёл по
Well, well, well, come on And who
трибунал А ну ну ну ну давай А кто и за
filed a statement in 2 years
2 года подал
that is, look again that is,
заявление то есть ещё раз смотри то есть
we are looking at so much news Yes,
мы смотрим столько новостей было Да вот
in this in the Luhansk region, how
в этом в Луганской области как
Kadyrovites in the occupied territories of
кадыровцы на оккупированных территориях
Russian girls
русских девушек
How many reports were there and that at least one
Сколько было сообщений и что хоть одного
Kadyrovite through the tribunal you
кадыровца через трибунал вы
them Well, let's not generalize the question Well, how
их Ну давайте не обобщать вопрос Ну как
not to feel they they look Kadyrovites Yes, stupidly, in
не оща они они смотри кадыровцы Да тупо
short, and how Kadyrovites
короче а как кадыровцы этого русского
beat up this Russian patrolman like somewhere in the
патрульного избили типа где-то в
Luhansk region or in Donetsk he
Луганской области или в Донецкой он их
stopped them said that in short there was an
остановил сказал что короче там
expired pass they went out gave him
просроченный пропуск они выш дали ему
just and the Armed Forces and went who did I for
просто и ВС и поехали кто сделал Я за
such  news And in Sevastopol
такими новостями А в се в Севастополе
these soldiers of yours went into a bar just people
эти вояки ваши зашли в бар просто людей
like butts and so on their heads they
типа прикладами и так на головах они
stand and
посто и
what Well, okay, if such a conversation your
что Ну хорошо если такой разговор ваши
troops on yours again look you Don't
войска по вашим же ещё раз смотри ты Не
jump off the topic I say Look who of
спрыгивать с темы Я говорю Смотри кто из
your Russians in 2 years went to
ваших русских за 2 года пошёл под
court for war crimes
трибунал за военные преступления
are there any officers who are
есть какие-то офицеры которые являются
traitors I can't name Traitor No
предателями я не могу назвать Преда Нет
for mockery of people I can
за издевательство над людьми могу
name the place where your troops
назвать место в котором ваши войска
fired on your own civilians Well,
обстреливали ваших же мирных А ну
tell me Come on, tell me from
расскажи Давай расскажи мне из
Kislovodsk in short where Our troops
Кисловодска короче где Наши войска
fired on civilians
обстреляли мирных
Come on Where from again from
Давай Откуда ещё раз из
Kislovodsk Pyatigorsk And I from
Кисловодска Пятигорска А я из
Kislovodsk decided to say Well,
Кисловодска решил сказать Ну
okay Cossack Lopan and what Cossack Lopan
хорошо казач Лопань и что Казачья Лопань
Well there were moments of shelling you were in the
Ну там были моменты обстрела ты был в
Cossack in Cossack
казачьей в Казачьей
Lopan No I have a friend there
Лопани Нет я у меня товарищ там был
Wait Stop stop stop stop stop come on come on come on
Подожди Стоп стоп стоп стоп стоп давай
comrade first of all I don't
так давай так товарищ во-первых Я не
know where the comrade got the information from the comrade the
знаю откуда у товарища информация
comrade said the comrade's girlfriend  a
товарищу товарищ сказал подруга товарища
friend there a drinking buddy
товарищу там собутыльник
like a partner told in short him and he
типа партнёр рассказал короче его а он
you an
тебе
argument you saw something Alexey
спор ты видел что-то Алексей
That is you don't want to squeeze this I'm
То есть ты не хочешь поджать эту Я
asking I'm asking I'm asking did you
спрашиваю Я спрашиваю Я спрашиваю ты
personally see
видел лично
this you saw
это ты видел
Personally I'll tell you Yes look I have
Лично я тебе скажу Да смотри у меня есть
a friend yes he says that Kadyrov saw a sheep how do
знакомый да он говорит что Кадыров овцу
you feel about this How do you feel
этому Как ты
about this I won't believe it Well
относишься я в это не поверю Ну Друг
I have a friend Tumso in Europe like he
тумсо у меня в Европе есть типа он
says that he saw a Kadyrovite I wo
говорит что он видел как кадыровцу
n't believe it Well what if you don't
я в это не поверю Ну а что ты не
believe in Kazachiy Lopa you do
поверишь в Казачий лопа не веришь А
n't believe And you don't believe Kadyrov a sheep And what is it Well
Кадырову овцу не веришь А что такое Ну
excuse me this is an influential person in the
ты извини меня это влиятельный человек в
Russian Federation Well that's it
Российской Федерации Ну так вот Вот
Exactly how
именно как
influential and not only that not just
влиятельный причём мало того не просто
somewhere there in a barn Yes
где-то там в сарае Да
publicly Well publicly well there is
публично Ну публично хорошо есть
some video
какое-то видео
or a dream they don't give out videos
или снить они видео не дают те потому
because of the phones You like How do you get up and
что телефоны Ты как Как ты встанешь и
Kadyrov you together with a sheep then you
Кадыров тебя вместе с овцой тогда
understand If you start filming in Nuno the
понимаешь Если ты будешь снимать во нуно
people who were present at this
люди которые присутствовали на этом
celebration they
празднике они это
saw it And  what Well, people told stories, you
видели И что Ну рассказы рассказывали
know, people told stories, and
люди понимаешь рассказывали люди и
what do you think about it Well, there's no
что как ты к этому относишься Ну нет
smoke without fire
дыма без огня
Why do you hate Kadyrov so much,
Почему вы так ненавидите Кадырова
explain And what do we hate I don't understand
объясни Да причём ненавидим Я не понимаю
why he abuses animals Well,
почему он издевается над животными Так
you do it well How come You haven't
ну ты этого же хорошо Как так Ты не
seen about lopaniye, you see, that's what we
видел про лопание видишь мы так и
say No, no Wait, no We don't remove it, we don't remove it,
говорим Да не не Подожди не Мы те не не
no, no, we Lopani and
убираем не убираем нет нет мы Лопани и
Kadyrov, let's finish talking, how are you, let's do it
Кадыров давай договорим это как ты давай
so well Do you admit that it could have been
так хорошо Ты допускаешь что могло быть
something like that for a
такое что
Kadyrovite, no, why
кадыровцу нет почему
because, well, there's the same rumor, no Well,
потому что ну есть такой же слух нет Ну
look, it's not all that clear-cut, but
смотри это ну не всё так однозначно но
if there are people who say that, then it
если есть люди которые так говорят
could have been like that Well,
значит могло так
okay, wait a second, now you
быть Ну хорошо подожди на секунду сейчас
're saying
говоришь
Come on I personally didn't see what happened in
Давай Я лично не видел то что было в
Kazach Lopan,
казач лопане
is it good, Vil, wait, you admit it
хоро ли этого Вил подожди ты допускаешь
Come on, you admit it, come on, you
Давай ты допуска ты давай так ты
admit it, by 1%, that it's true that
допускаешь на 1% что это правда что
Kadyrov is a kazu No, I don't admit it in
Кадыров казу Нет я этого не допускаю ни
any form, by half a percent, you admit it,
в каком виде на полпроцента допускаешь
cash on the floor, zero, bro  zero no Well
нал на пол на ноль братан ноль не Ну
why not well
почему не ну
how did the connection start to disappear yes right away Well
как пропадать связь стала да сразу Ну
look well really really so that is I do
смотри ну реально реально так то есть я
n't know what kind of custom is it there he has
не знаю что это за обычай там у него
such yes like it turns out Well they say
такой да типа получается Ну вот говорят
Yes what is he talking about lying this No well it was a dedication
он про лож это Не ну это было посвещение
pos dedication to the head of the Republic Yes he's
пос посвящение На главы Республики Да он
like And this is not a kaza it was a
типа А это не каза это баран был да
ram yes a ram yes He was like saying that
барашик да Во он типа говорил что
look this ram symbolizes the
смотрите это этот баран символизирует
Russians Yes And now I'm from the Russian
русских Да И вот я сейчас от Русского
ram well this is generally nonsense Well so this is and
барана ну это вообще бред Ну так это вот
and he
и и он
said information you understand you tell me you tell me I didn't
сказал информаци понимаешь ты мне говори
see there And now you're talking about the fact that
виде А сейчас ты говоришь о том что
Kadyrov did something why are you
Кадыров что-то делал зачем ты это
saying this why are you hu pra I didn't see with
говоришь для чего ты ху пра я не видел
my own
своими
eyes you didn't see with yours wait look Wait look well
глазами ты не видел своми жди смотри
this
Подожди смотри ну мне же рассказал это
person told me He couldn't lie so
человек Он же не мог брехать значит у
he has a reason for this
него есть основание такое
Tell me how do I know Well it's like your
Говори откуда я знаю Ну это как твой
friend like here he is like my friend Well
друг типа вот он типа это мой друг Ну
okay I don't you hear
хорошо я ты не слышь
Me if he says this that he saw well
Ме если он это говорит что он видел ну
really well  how can we
реально ну как мы можем
doubt wait okay wait I'll tell you
сомневаться подожди хорошо стой я тебе
again come on you agree that one in a
раз давай ты согласен что один из
million can still be that it's
миллиона всё равно может быть что это
true that Kadyrov I don't agree at all Well how Well
правда что Кадыров я вообще не согласен
one in a million
Ну как Ну один из миллиона
just come on tact I agree that in
только давай такты согласен что в
society there are people who sleep with
обществе есть люди которые спят с
animals Well somewhere in the West probably not Well
животными Ну где-то на западе наверное
come on in Russia In Russia there are also
не Ну давай так в России В России тоже
convicts I personally have
есть осуждённые Своими глазами это лично
n't seen this I can't for this but okay And have you
не видел я не могу за это а хорошо А ты
seen it sometime No And you are in Russia Well
видел когда-то Нет А ты в России есть Ну
probably you see you I haven't seen it with my own eyes
наверное видиш ты Своими глазами не
but you can also say the same and about me I
видел но можешь утверждать тоже и про ми
said probably these are different things When
сказал наверно это разные вещи Когда
exactly and I said Probably you're not sure that
точно а я гово Наверно ты не уверен что
in Russia there are
в России есть
vi Do you think there are in Russia
ви Как думаешь в России
I don't know I haven't
есть я не знаю я не
seen I've generally squeezed you in
видел я тебя вообще зажал
short Because you were involved
короче Потому что ты
in the topic with Kadyrov when I
знался за тему с Кадыровым когда я тебе
tell you that
говорю что
ho I got hooked because very Schwab the
хо я зацепился потому что очень Шваб
topic immediately so know cylindrical
тема сразу тако зна цилиндрические
forms Listen to me for a second you
формы Послушай меня на секунду ты же
can have respect for the interlocutor and
можешь иметь уважение к собеседнику и
listen to him no I can't have I have the
слушать его нет могу не иметь имею
right then we have nothing to talk about no
право тогда нам не о чем разговарить не
well wait  look where in the law it is written
ну подожди смотри Где в законе написано
here is there some kind of Constitution or a
вот есть какой-то Конституция или там
law that you are obliged to listen to the interlocutor
закон что обязан выслушать собеседника
there is no such
нет такого
law there is no I agree Well
закона нету я согласен Ну человеческое у
you should have a human wait And what is
тебя должно быть подожди А что такое
human For example for me Yes here
человеческое Например у меня Да вот у
we have a human concept that citizens of the
нас человеческие понятие что э граждан
Russian Federation can be
Российской Федерации можно
interrupted And everything is all No Bazaar
перебивать А всё всё Базара нет до
goodbye do your business then on
свидания занимайте своим делом то на
Kadyrov
кадырове
No buddy Kadyrov is a normal
свае Нет дружище Кадыров нормальный
person well wait come on do you agree
человек ну подожди давай так ты согласен
that there are people in the world who are
что в мире есть люди
sheep I don't know this and you don't know
баранами Я не знаю этого а не знаешь
right away Yes a long time
сразу
ago if probably some
Да даве если наверно какой-нибудь
Russian Ukrainian let's let's admit let's admit
русский украинкой давайте давай мы допу
Look But you know what the most
давайте Смотри Но знаешь что самое
important thing I will say the most important thing is that you
главное я скажу самое главное что ты
said about Kady This is what you
говорил о Кады Вот это со мной
were talking about with me You didn't say no and didn't
разговаривал Ты не сказал нет и не
switch immediately you admitted that
переключился сразу ты допустил что
Ramzan Lakhma Yes it was discussed in such a
Рамзан лахма Да обсуждался в таком
negative
негативном
way So I proved to you that this did not
ключе Так я тебе доказывал что такого не
happen because I didn't sl You should have
было потому что я такого не сл Ты должен
you should Look when someone
был ты должен Смотри когда кто-то
says such things about Ramzan Lakhma tovi you need to
говорит такое о рамзане лахма тови нужно
switch immediately if you
сразу переключаться если ты вступаешь в
you are entering this discussion already look you
эту дискуссию ты уже смотри ты 5 минут
did the broadcast for 5 minutes in that you were proving yes
так делал эфир в том что доказывал да
or no And what will people remember Kadyrov and a
или нет А что люди запомнят Кадыров и
ram yes It turns out they will not remember whether it was
баран да Получается они же не запомнят
or not and someone doubts
было или не было а кто-то за сомневается
Or maybe it really
А может и действительно так
was like that Well you said I
было Ну ты же говорил я тебя
slammed you and then Kadyrov will think something like that
слм а потом Кадыров такое подумает
Listen wait something This Alexey
Слушай подожди что-то Этот Алексей
Nesterov in short Very little not quite
Нестеров короче Очень немного не совсем
fiercely
яро меня
defended me probably at his 32 years old
защищал наверное ему в его 32 года не
life is not so fun I am just saying that
так весело живётся Я просто говорю что
this
тако
would be in my opinion and the opinion of others Lyuda NT
бы по мое мнению а мнение других Люде НТ
That is, you admitted that other people
То есть ты допустил что другие люди
can think such things about Ramzan Lakhma Tovi
могут такое думать о рамзане лахма тови
yes I dont know what they can you understand this is a
да я не знаю что они могут понимаешь это
personal opinion they are free people They
лично мнение они свободные люди Они
want to think about
хотят думать об
this how long is your city to Grozny by car by car
этого сколько твоего города до Грозного
how long is it from
времени по времени сколько езды от
your city to Grozny I dont know Well
твоего города до Грозного Я не знаю Ну
find out approximately I have never specified this it will be
примерно узнай Я никогда не уточнял это
useful to specify
это пригодится уточнить
now once again I would advise specifying
сейчас ещё раз я б советовал уточнить на
just in case to know
всякий случай чтобы знать
uh time  travel If by motorcade yes from
ээ время проезда Если кортежем да от
your city to Grozny
твоего города до Грозного
Yeah this will be very useful information
Угу это будет очень полезная информация
for you and your
для тебя и твоих
relatives Okay I
родственников Хорошо я
Yakhin immediately Cossack lopa they were there you were
Яхин сразу Казачий лопа они вот там вы
shooting a friend said yes And here like a
стреляли друг говорил да А тут типа Мне
friend told me about no not right away all
друг говорил о не не сразу сё
hello good night Where are you
здравствуйте доброй ночи Вы
from Russia Rostov And you are from the States Yes I
откуда Россия Ростов А вы Штатов Да я
myself am from Rostov but not that Rostov but
сам родом из Ростова но не того Ростова
another and now I live in California 18
а другого а сейчас живу в Калифорнии 18
years Yeah in 2 years it will be the Twentieth
лет Угу через 2 года будет Двадцатый
great what do you
замечательно кем
work as a
работаете я
driver Trucker or taxi driver who no no
водителем Дальнобойщик или таксист кто
so on on a
так на на
Gazelle Gazelle is an animal or what I didn't
Газели Газель - это животное или что не
understand No it's a make of car and a
понял Нет это марка автомобиля а
small GAZ truck I understood I wonder
газ грузовичок небольшой понял Интересно
what are you talking about here now roulettes what
а чём тут общаетесь сейчас рулетки что
brought you here so late in the evening
вас привело в столь поздний вечер
Well I'm trying to communicate with Ukrainians
сюда Ну пытаюсь с украинцами пообщаться
they are not adequate I tried the same thing there I
они не адекватно Я про я пробовал тоже
put a flag Ukraine Yes in order to
вот я там ставил флажок Украину Да чтобы
communicate with them they I'm saying
с ними пообщаться они Я вот говорю
look I'm Russian but I live in America how do
смотрите Я русский но живу в Америке как
you treat me they are aggressive
Вы ко мне относитесь они агрессивные
right away Yes I kind of treat any people
сразу Да я как бы К любым людям
from the beginning eh well  as a person
изначально отношусь э ну как к человеку
with A what do you think Yes why do
с А как вы Как вы считаете Да почему
Ukrainians
украинцы нас
hate us Well why Well first of all
ненавидят Ну почему Ну во-первых
Their propaganda is very strong I also
Пропаганда у них очень сильная я тоже
say Dash
говорю Даш
Well we are and I anyway I do
ну мы-то вот и я как бы там ни было я им
n't wish them death I don't wish them bad I
не желаю смерти я им не желаю плохого я
wish them good and they
им Желаю хорошего а они
I also look I communicate with them I say
Я тоже смотрите я им общаюсь говорю
look our missiles are flying Yes they Well it
смотрите наши ракеты летят Да они Ну
turns out that they destroyed
получается так что уничтожили там
Mariupol there destroyed part of Kharkov there
Мариуполь уничтожили часть Харькова там
Donetsk Lugansk there Bakhmut yes Well damn well so
Донецк Луганск там бахмут да Ну это блин
what I basically think that
ну ну и что я я в принципе считаю что
our Russian missiles are not a
наши российские ракеты - это ещё не
reason to hate us
повод нас ненавидеть
really not Well here a little You are wrong Well how
правда не Ну тут чуть-чуть Вы не правы
wait stop don't look Well we still well
Ну как подожди стоп не смотри Ну мы всё
You saw what kind of destruction we are
равно ну Ты же видел какие мы разрушения
doing in Kharkov in Bakhmut we
делаем в Харькове в бахмуте бахмут мы
completely leveled Bakhmut I have a classmate Sanya
вообще сравняли у меня Одноклассник Саня
Prokhorov Yes he moved to Ukraine and
Прохоров да он переехал был в Украину и
lived in Bakhmut in Bakhmut he
в бахмуте жил в бахмуте
lived on it flew in If the Russian everything
жил по нему прилетел Каб российский всё
died there were no Bakhmuts left  all
погиб бахмута не осталось всех всех
people our Russian people there lived
людей наши русские люди там жили
Russian-speaking Well, very Sobol
русскоязычные Ну очень Соболе
and why I just don't understand I don't understand
а зачем Я просто не понимаю Я не понимаю
why we can't hit Washington
почему мы не можем ударить по вашингтону
Berlin London to
по Берлину по лондону чтобы всё
finish everything volume on Russian-speaking cities
закончить объём по русскоязычных городах
Kharkov Mariupol
Харьков Мариуполь
Bakhmut
бахмут
Well Well how can I
Ну Ну как вам
tell you we are not fighting with Washington not with
сказать мы воюем не с вашингтоном не с
London not with Rome we are fighting with Ukraine no
лондоном не с римом воюем с Украиной нет
how small Ukraine is don't disgrace us
как маленькая Украина вы не позорьте
now you say with Russia that we are fighting with
сейчас с россиею говорите что мы воюем с
Ukraine we are fighting with the entire NATO bloc more
Украиной мы воюем со всем блоком НАТО
aggressively NATO bloc which since the
агрессивнее блоком НАТО который ещё со
times of the Soviet Union wanted our
времён Советского Союза желал нашего
destruction so or not you are a
уничтожения так или не так вы же
Soviet person I was
Советский человек я восемьдесят первого
born in 1981
года рождения Вы
What am I sixty-ninth sixty-
какого я шестьдесят девятого шестьдесят
ninth You definitely uh you uh understand the evil
девятого Вы точно ээ вы э понимаете злой
grin of American imperialism they
оскал американского империализма они
created NATO what for they Placed
создали НАТО для чего они Разместили
missiles in Turkey Yes NATO
ракеты в Турции Да
they drove us out of Eastern
натовские они вытеснили нас из Восточной
Europe they took
Европы они этому горбачёву взяли там
some money from this Gorbachev I don't know what they gave
какие-то или деньги я не знаю что они
him  they added something or what He went crazy Well, it was
ему подсыпали или что что Он сдурел Ну
n't they who forced him out, but rather
ну там не они вытеснили а скорее
Gorbachev himself left there no look
Горбачёв сам оттуда ушёл нет смотри
Gorbachev went Gorbachev Yes look he
Горбачёв поехал Горбачёв Да смотрите
went to met Reagan in America they
поехал в встретился с рейганом в Америке
took him around the supermarkets Yes they gave him
его поводили там по супермаркетам Да
Like chewing gum Gin these Soviet
дали Типа жвачки Джин вот эти советские
oh American ones they gave him to touch he has a
ой американские потрогать подарили у
wife this Raisa Sergeevna
него же жена вот эта Раиса Сергеевна
Gorbacheva remember he dragged her everywhere I was
Горбачёва помните он всюду её таскал я
little I remember he dragged her flew
маленький был я помню он её таскал летал
to Washington Yes with Raisa Sergeevna
в Вашингтон Да с раисой сергеевной
Why and she there bought fashionable clothes BT Gal Tere
Почему а она там шмотки модные БТ Гал
American without hanging out didn't even say
американский не зависая не даже сказал
why do these Ukrainians hate Russians I
почему же эти украинцы ненавидят россиян
wonder subscribe to my Telegram right
интересно подпишись на мий Telegram прям
now he and
зараз он а
Popik this is very and very important YouTube is
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
busy with us through scarg org in your ban and
заня нас через скарг орг в твый бан и
very many videos are not shown to people
дуже багато видео не показуе людям
at times vkazue information about streams to that
вчасно вказуе информация про стримы тому
for that we Mali operational links
для того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and while there in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video also interesting and useful
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we will oblige you to keep
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
constant operational links
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись
with
с